metdental.com 2002-12-09

# Legal Notices

Our Privacy Policy  
MetLife, Inc. (MetLife) is dedicated to helping protect you and those you love. Part of that protection includes safeguarding personal information about you that you have provided to us. MetLife's information practices for this website are outlined below.

Your Personal Information:  
When you come to a MetLife website, we log your current Internet address (this is usually a temporary address assigned by your Internet service provider when you sign in), the type of operating system you are using, and the type of browser software used. In addition, we may keep track of what portions of the website you are visiting. We aggregate this information to help us create a better experience for users of our website. For example: we may upgrade those parts of the website that are heavily visited or optimize the website to work more efficiently with certain operating systems. 

If you do choose to provide us with personal information, you can be assured that all information that you provide to us is kept in secure databases. MetLife treats this information as confidential. However, we may use this information for administrative and marketing purposes, and the information may be shared with our affiliates and, in some instances, unaffiliated third parties. For example, we may contact you to make you aware of MetLife products and/or services offered by MetLife, or its affiliates, which we feel may be of interest to you. We may disclose information to affiliates or unaffiliated third parties for the purpose of performing business services for us or as otherwise permitted by law. We will not sell or otherwise make available personal information about you to unaffiliated third parties for marketing purposes, except as permitted or required by law. You may contact us at the addresses listed below in order to tell us not to share your personal information with our affiliates or unaffiliated third parties for marketing purposes.

Cookies:  
A cookie is a small piece of information that a website sends to your computer, which is stored in a file on your hard drive. The next time you visit our website, we may use the information stored in the cookie file to facilitate your use of our website. For example, we may use the cookie file to store a password so that you do not have to continually input it every time you move to a different section of a password-protected portion of our website. A cookie does not tell us your individual identity unless you have chosen to provide it to us. Most cookies expire after a defined period of time, or you can delete your cookie file at any time you choose. In addition, you can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie so that you can decide whether to accept or reject it.

Privacy and E-Mail:  
Not every website takes steps to safeguard the privacy of your information. In particular, if you need to send confidential information and are unsure about the security of a website, then you should consider sending it by phone or by regular mail instead. E-mail on the Internet is not secure unless you are using a secure e-mail program. If any organization or individual asks you for confidential information (your Social Security Number or a bank or credit card account number, for example), you should check to see if the information being transmitted is encrypted in order to ensure the security of your information. You can check to see whether your information is encrypted by checking the bottom line of your browser window. If a broken key or open lock is displayed, then the information is not being scrambled (or encrypted) when it is sent over the Internet. If the key or lock is broken or open, then the information being transmitted is not encrypted and it is possible for it to be intercepted and read by an unauthorized party.

Minors:  
At the MetLife websites, we make no active effort to collect personal information from children under the age of 18. We believe that children who do wish to submit information to MetLife should have permission from their parent or legal guardian, and we encourage you to participate in your child's exploration of the Internet.

Contact Information:  
If you have any questions about MetLife's information practices, you can contact: 

MetLife, Inc.  
Electronic Commerce  
One Madison Avenue, 24A  
New York, NY 10010  
Attn: Online Privacy Director  
or  
or  
1-800-638-5433
